do you know what odoo crm is in this
video we are going to explain how odoo
crm is helping businesses to manage
their customers leads and opportunities
crm is a strategy technique and
technology tool for managing all your
company relationship and interaction
with customer major problems that an
organization faces while managing their
customers cluttered customer data low
customer retention rate inefficient
tracking and reporting slow growth rate
odoo can solve all of them odoo crm is a
tool that is focused on building better
relationships with customers odoo crm is
a robust solution that helps you enhance
customer experience and nurture
relationships with your potential
customers as well as existing customers
furthermore odoo crm is closely
integrated with other odoo modules like
sales purchase e-commerce website
marketing and inventory this crm
software is built for tackling modern
challenges that businesses face such as
marketing customer service communication
let's dive into the powerful features of
odoo crm we will discuss the features
one by one sell faster with modern user
interface mobile friendly solution
reducing redundant data entry large
screen view bleeds is a major feature of
odoo crm which helps you with the lead
nurturing bleed scoring online
acquisition url tracker
next feature of the crm in the row is
opportunities helps you with the
activity management pipeline management
customize stage schedule meetings add
your customers in just a few clicks in
your address book add customer
preference manage multiple address of
them track customer history communicate
efficiently with the help of email
templates email automation email gateway
custom alert fetch reports with an easy
to understand dashboard opportunities
analysis cohort analysis bleed analysis
and integration the integration will
help you improve customer relationships
maintain customer data increase sales
with quote to order capabilities and
deliver better customer service odoocrm
helps you to manage your business at
your fingertips with mobile application
and tablets
how odoo crm is different from other crm
providing companies
odoo crm provides certain advantages
such as less expensive third-party
ecosystem ease of use modular suited for
small and medium-sized enterprises odoo
crm that salespeople loves try it today
for more info visit our website
www.o2btechnologies.com
or contact us at info at o2b
technologies dot com o2 o2ba silver
partner to odoo
thanks for watching don't forget to like
share and subscribe